export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2021 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2012q.pdf",
        solution: "2101a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University, Ankara" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Kadyr Annabayev", affiliation: "Turkmen State Institute of Architecture and Construction, Ashkabat" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Halil Özkan", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Ömer Topaloğlu", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2101q.pdf",
        solution: "2102a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Mehmet Burak Gönül", affiliation: "Cağaloğlu Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Mehmet Özgün Cihangir", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Chui Tsz Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Tan Özalp", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yılmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Kipp Johnson", affiliation: "Beaverton, Oregon, USA" },
            { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
            { name: "Atilla Akkuş", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Teknik Okulları, Kocaeli" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ankara" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Çağla Çam", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Teknik Okulları, Kocaeli" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Omar Sonebi", affiliation: "Lycee technique Settat, Casablanca, Morocco" },
            { name: "Muhammetmyrat Gochmyradov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy School, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yazlyyev", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy School, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2102q.pdf",
        solution: "2103a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Barış Koyuncu", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Mehmet Burak Gönül", affiliation: "Cağaloğlu Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2103q.pdf",
        solution: "2104a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Alp Eren Köken", affiliation: "Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi, Antalya" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Kadyr Annabayev", affiliation: "Turkmen State Institute of Architecture and Construction, Ashkabat" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Yusuf Kağan Çiçekdağ", affiliation: "İzmir Özel 29 Mayıs Bornova Fen Lisesi" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2104q.pdf",
        solution: "2105a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Chui Tsz Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
            { name: "Kadyr Annabayev", affiliation: "Turkmen State Institute of Architecture and Construction, Ashkabat" },
            { name: "Mehran Hosseini-Pishrobat", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mountassir Farid", affiliation: "Awalee Consulting, Paris, France" },
            { name: "Alp Eren Köken", affiliation: "Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi, Antalya" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2105q.pdf",
        solution: "2106a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yılmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Ata Özgür Durak", affiliation: "Muğla" },
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Aydın" },
            { name: "Atilla Akkuş", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Teknik Okulları, Kocaeli" },
            { name: "Gurt Devletov", affiliation: "State Energy Institute, Mary, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Çağla B. Çam", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Anadolu Teknik Lisesi, Kocaeli" },
            { name: "Muhammetmyrat Gochmyradov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy School, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Fatih Demir", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Omar Sonebi", affiliation: "Lycee technique Settat, Casablanca, Morocco" },
            { name: "Gürkan Koray Akpınar", affiliation: "Efeler, Aydın" },
            { name: "Alp Eren Köken", affiliation: "Antalya Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2106q.pdf",
        solution: "2108a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Gurt Devletov", affiliation: "State Energy Institute, Mary, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Tan Özalp", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "İmre Özbay", affiliation: "Eser Telekom & NANOTAM, Bilkent" },
            { name: "Metin Can Aydemir", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Orkhan Ashrafov", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Mehmet Burak Gönül", affiliation: "Cağaloğlu Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "UNIST, Korea" },
            { name: "Adem Limani", affiliation: "Lund University, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Rainer Müller", affiliation: "Ludwigsburg, Germany" },
            { name: "Daniel Salehi", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Max Nilsson", affiliation: "Lund University, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2108q.pdf",
        solution: "2109a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Myrat Chashemov", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Erciyes University" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Barış Koyuncu", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Burak Buğra Önder", affiliation: "İstanbul Erkek Lisesi" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2109q.pdf",
        solution: "2110a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Lujain Qazmanny", affiliation: "Jordan" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2110q.pdf",
        solution: "2111a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Halil İbrahim Kanpak", affiliation: "Koç University" },
            { name: "Gurt Devletov", affiliation: "State Energy Institute, Mary, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ozan Cem Baş", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Aydın" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Özel İzmir Bahçeşehir Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Leyla Cafarova", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Lujain Qazmanny", affiliation: "Jordan" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yılmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Hüseyin Ege Olcay", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Gürkan Koray Akpınar", affiliation: "Efeler, Aydın" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2021,
        question: "2111q.pdf",
        solution: "2112a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Gurt Devletov", affiliation: "State Energy Institute, Mary, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Aydın" },
            { name: "Lujain Qazmanny", affiliation: "Jordan" },
            { name: "Leyla Cafarova", affiliation: "Azerbaijan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    }
];
